Not every intervention is divine.
Immaculate is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Michael Mohan.
An American nun embarks on a new journey when she joins a
remote convent in the Italian countryside.
However, her warm welcome quickly turns into a living nightmare when she discovers
her new home harbours a sinister secret and unspeakable horrors.
Sister Cecilia, played by Sydney Sweeney.
Father Sal Tedeschi, played by Álvaro Morte.
Sister Mary, played by Simona Tabasco.
Sister Gwen, played by Benedetta Porcaroli.
Cardinal Franco Merola, played by Giorgio Colangeli.
Mother Superior, played by Dora Romano.
Immaculate is a 2024 American horror film  directed by
Michael Mohan and written by Andrew Lobel.
It stars Sydney Sweeney (who also produced), Álvaro Morte, Benedetta
Porcaroli, Dora Romano, Giorgio Colangeli, and Simona Tabasco.
The plot focuses on a young novice nun, who is invited to reside at a picturesque
Italian convent, but slowly realizes the terrifying secrets it harbors.
Immaculate premiered at South by Southwest on March 12, 2024, and was released
theatrically in the United States by Neon on March 22, 2024.
The film received mostly positive reviews and grossed $35 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of nun, italy, pregnancy, priest, female protagonist.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.